thechunkychef.com 2018-10-21

# Copyright & Privacy - The Chunky Chef

### **Content Sharing Policy:**

All of the content, including recipes, and photographs, published on The Chunky Chef is property of The Chunky Chef (Amanda Batcher).

I publish these recipes so you can share them and encourage others to try them, however, if you would like to share a recipe and/or photo on your website, you may share a photo with a LINK BACK to the original recipe, giving The Chunky Chef full credit.

Directly copying and pasting recipes originally posted here, on The Chunky Chef, onto your website is strictly prohibited.

### **Copyright Policy:**

© The Chunky Chef 2015-2018. Unauthorized use and/or duplication of this material and/or photographs without expressed written permission from this site’s author and/or owner is strictly prohibited. EXCERPTS and LINKS may be used, provided that full and clear credit is given to The Chunky Chef, with appropriate and specific direction to the original content.

### **Affiliate Link/Product Policy:**

The Chunky Chef is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com.

So, what does that mean exactly?  I’ve partnered with Amazon to share with you certain products that are recommended to me, or that I personally own and LOVE.  If you click  on the link or image provided and purchase from the amazon page it opens up, I will receive a small commission.  There will NEVER be any extra cost to you!  I whole-heartedly thank you for supporting The Chunky Chef and brands I love 🙂

## **Privacy Policy:**

**At thechunkychef.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is essential. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit thechunkychef.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.**

This privacy policy sets out how The Chunky Chef, LLC uses and protects any information that you give while using www.thechunkychef.com

Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, which is the company on your internet bill), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Safari or Chrome, etc), the time you visited our site, and which pages you visited throughout our site.

### What we do with the information we gather

We may ask for information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services. 
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. 

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

### Advertising

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. We may use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the website, including [AdThrive](http://www.adthrive.com/). These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data.  The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and The Chunky Chef, LLC disclaims all liability in connection therewith.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/)

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

_**Use of this website indicates that you accept this policy.**_  If you have any other questions about the data we collect and why, please contact us at amanda@thechunkychef.com

_The Chunky Chef, LLC  may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.  The last update made to this page was on May 15, 2018._
